I'm going to show you how to make a Bluebird.
Now this drink is stirred and not shaken so you don't need much ice.
So take it put it in to your glass.
You're going to add an ounce and half of gin.
So get your jigger.
Pour in an ounce, flip it over and add the half of ounce.
Then you're going to add an ounce of trip sec, actually half an ounce of triple sec.
Just grab that.
To the small side of the jigger.
You're going to do an half an ounce of blue Curacao.
Despite it's blue flavor, it has an orange taste behind it.
Then you're going to add a couple dashes of bitters so have that handy.
Do just a couple.
That should be good.
And then you're going to stir it so have your stirrer available.
Put it in and twist it around just like that.
Looks good.
Then you're going to strain it in to a glass.
So, grab your glass, have your stainer available and gently pout it in.
Just like so.
And you're going to garnish this with a cherry and a lemon twist, that you can twist.
Pour in just like that, put in your straw and then you have a Blue Bird.